<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on God is Good</title>
    <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on God is Good</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://godisgood.io/docs/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/about/</guid>
      <description>Why I Wrote God is Good # The &amp;ldquo;God is Good&amp;rdquo; Book was a dream conceived around 2010 by Harold J. Duarte-Bernhardt who was a Senior Pastor of &amp;ldquo;Life Center&amp;rdquo; in Hollywood, CA. “Life Center” is not a denomination, it’s not a religion, it’s simply a movement rooted in John 10:10. “I have come,&amp;quot; said Jesus, “that you may have LIFE and have it more abundantly!&amp;quot; Extravagant LIFE, in the frame of a magnificent God who wants to bless His followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I Trust God?</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/can-i-trust-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/can-i-trust-god/</guid>
      <description>Can the Bible be Trusted? # What is the Bible all about? #  Jesus said, &amp;ldquo;You are busy analyzing the Scriptures, poring over them hoping to gain eternal life. Everything you read points to me&amp;rdquo; (John 5:39, TPT) The Bible is a love story from God. It contains the words of God, a story about humanity&amp;rsquo;s struggle and God&amp;rsquo;s love.
 Sorry, your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos.   The Bible Explained: So Simple, Even a Child Will Get It</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Purpose</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos.    Have You Read God&amp;rsquo;s Love Letter to you? FathersLoveLetter.com
Your heavenly Father has a plan for each of our individual lives. To fulfill that plan is nothing less than ultimate success in life. But we need to hear Him, so that He can lead us into His plan for our lives. But to do that, we need to be connected to Him through a personal loving relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Identity</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-identity/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos.    God is the Creator of all things. The source. The beginning. The genesis. The alpha. He is beyond our comprehension. We catch glimpses of God here and there. We mostly know what God is like, because Jesus came to this earth 2.000 years to reveal the heart of God. His passion for humanity! To understand God we must study Jesus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Life Has Value</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-life-has-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/your-life-has-value/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of your age at this moment, God has been watching you since the day you were born. God has been allowing things to happen or not to happen. There is no room for arrogance in God’s universe. Yes, you made choices, but your choices were enabled because God let it happen! When God chooses to override your freedom of choice, you are DONE, Friend! God is the supreme manager of the entire universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power of Belief</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/power-of-belief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/power-of-belief/</guid>
      <description>When Jesus was crucified, it was an enormous shock to His followers. They secretly expected Him to establish His kingdom on earth when pushed against the wall! They saw how Jesus was mistreated. To the last moment, they waited for a divine manifestation of power to take care of Jesus, and prove to the world He was indeed the Messiah, the liberator of the Jewish nation. They figured out that if Jesus was able to heal the sick, provide food to crowds out of nothing, wine out of water, He could also perform a miracle in His behalf!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God is Good</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-is-good/</guid>
      <description>God is beyond our imagination. I have always loved contrasts. I am fascinated by contrasts and opposites. It intrigues me.
 God is the superlative of contrasts and extremes. If you define the &amp;ldquo;ends&amp;rdquo; of God, with &amp;ldquo;poles&amp;rdquo; like the south and the north pole, God&amp;rsquo;s extremes would go so far, that would would never see both ends. Beyond your wildest imagination is God!  Who Is God? Your browser does not support the audio element.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God is Simple</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-is-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-is-simple/</guid>
      <description>Religion teaches you that you have to do a bunch of things to reach perfection in the eyes of God. Nothing could ever be further from the truth of God! You are born forgiven, though imperfect. If you believe and walk on the state of perfection God has declared for you, you will die forgiven, though imperfect. You are perfect by God&amp;rsquo;s TOTAL, complete forgiveness, though you will always remain imperfect as a human being!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God Cares</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/god-cares/</guid>
      <description>GOD CARES! GOD LOVES YOU! GOD WANTS YOU TO SUCCEED! All of our teachings, studies, conversations are rooted in that one single principle. That&amp;rsquo;s why we don&amp;rsquo;t believe in RELIGION. We believe that a RELATIONSHIP WITH GOD will make you understand how much God loves you! Once you get that in your brain, the rest is easy stuff! Religion and denominations make it complicated, God wants you and I to understand the basics!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gospel is Good News</title>
      <link>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/gospel-good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://godisgood.io/docs/book/gospel-good-news/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos.    People are not going to fully appreciate the good news until they first know the bad news. The bad news is that we have ALL have sinned against God and have fallen short of His standards. Good and bad people alike! Our nature is fragmented, stubborn, selfish, self-centered. Our condition, just by breathing on this planet and having our parents genes, is SINFUL.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
